voicenation.com 2017-06-06

# VoiceNation | Privacy Policy

VoiceNation d/b/a QualityAnsweringService.com (“VoiceNation”) is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you a powerful and safe online experience. By using the VoiceNation web site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for VoiceNation’s QualityAnsweringService.com web site. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**About the QualityAnsweringService.com Service**

VoiceNation, through its QualityAnsweringService.com web site, provides functionality enabling our members to make use of powerful and flexible answering service solutions, including but not limited to receptionist services, call screening, live message relay, disaster recovery, and simple order taking and order fulfillment.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

VoiceNation collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number. VoiceNation also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by VoiceNation. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. This information is used by VoiceNation for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the QualityAnsweringService.com web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through VoiceNation public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

VoiceNation encourages you to review the privacy statements of web sites you choose to link to from VoiceNation so that you can understand how those web sites collect, use, and share your information. VoiceNation is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on web sites outside of the VoiceNation or QualityAnsweringService.com family of web sites.

**Use of your Personal Information**

VoiceNation collects and uses your personal information to operate the QualityAnsweringService.com web site and deliver the services you have requested. VoiceNation also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from VoiceNation and its affiliates. VoiceNation may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

VoiceNation does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. VoiceNation may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party, without your permission. In addition, VoiceNation may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to VoiceNation, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

VoiceNation does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

VoiceNation keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within VoiceNation, in order to determine which VoiceNation services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within VoiceNation to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

VoiceNation will disclose your personal information without notice only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on VoiceNation or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of VoiceNation; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of VoiceNation, or the public.

**Contests and Promotions**

On various occasions, VoiceNation sponsors contests, surveys or promotions or allows other companies to sponsor contests or promotions on our site. In order to enter a contest or promotion, you would be asked to provide personally identifiable information. For all contests and promotions sponsored by VoiceNation, the information you submit will be treated in the same way we would treat your new member information.

If a promotion is sponsored by a third party, then it will clearly indicate who is collecting the personal information, and you will be given an opportunity to volunteer your information where you will have a choice whether to disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties. These third parties may have their own policies for handling personal information, and information you submit will be subject to those policies. Although VoiceNation encourages third parties to adhere to appropriate privacy standards and policies, we are not responsible for the actions or policies of such parties.

**Our Sponsors and Business Partners**

Our sponsors, from time to time, offer you the opportunity to sign up for their services or information, such as newsletters or promotions. In these instances, we will clearly inform you about exactly who is collecting what personally identifiable information requested by the sponsor, and we will ask you to opt-in and give your permission to release your information to the sponsor prior to disclosing your personal information. If you consent, VoiceNation will transfer your information to the sponsor. Once your information has been transferred to the sponsor, VoiceNation is not responsible for its use. The sponsor's use of the information is governed by the sponsor's privacy policy. While we encourage our third party sponsors to adhere to appropriate privacy standards, we are not responsible for the actions or policies of our sponsors.

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what personal data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any personal data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any personal data we have about you.
  * Express any concerns regarding our use of your personal data.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line in the email, or email our Customer Service Desk.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done on our Settings page, or by emailing our Customer Service Desk.

Users of our site are notified wherever possible in the event that their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

**Use of Cookies**

The QualityAnsweringService.com web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize QualityAnsweringService.com pages, or register with QualityAnsweringService.com, a cookie helps VoiceNation to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same QualityAnsweringService.com web page, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the QualityAnsweringService.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the QualityAnsweringService.com services or web sites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

VoiceNation takes commercially reasonable steps to secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. VoiceNation secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Changes to this Statement**

VoiceNation will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. VoiceNation encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how VoiceNation is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

VoiceNation welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that VoiceNation has not adhered to this Statement, please contact VoiceNation at [info@qualityansweringservice.com](mailto:info@qualityansweringservice.com?subject=Privacy%2520Policy%2520Inquiry). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
